Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Born-Digital Photographs, 1999-2019
  - Portraits, 2006 June 1-2016 July 15; 7; 1296 Digital Files
    - Portraits, 2006 June 1-2016 July 15; 7.1; 1296 Digital Files
      - Portrait of Vicky Rizzo, 2004...
      - Portrait of Jim Sammons, 2004...
      - Portrait of Shobha Smith, 2004...
      - Portrait of Albin Zak, 2004...
      - Portrait of Gail Berley, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Eric Block, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Adrienne Bonilla, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Shai Brown, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Ida Canty, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Cheng Chen, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Joan Cipperly, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Judy Coleman, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Sharon Danoff-Burg, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Helen Desfosses, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Kevin Doolen, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Sue Faerman, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Ingrid Fisher, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Jim Fleming, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Laurie Garafola, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Judy Genshaft, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Garreth Griffiths, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Maureen Helmer, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Colin Izzard, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Robert Jarvenpa, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Bruce Kingma, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Tim Lance, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Raef Lawson, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Wayne Locust, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Wendall Lorang, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Jaume Marti-Olivella, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Joseph Mascarenhas, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Bruce Miroff, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Bob Nolan, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of ?? O'Connell, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Luis Paris, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Marina Petrukhina, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Suzanne Phillips, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Robert Purtell, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Mark Raider, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Barbara Ritter, 2005...
      - Portrait of Amy Tucker, 2005...
      - Portrait of Robert D. McEvoy, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Hugh Johnson, c. 2006...
      - Portrait of Robert Lazare, 2006...
      - Portrait of Patricia Strach, 2006...
      - Portrait of William Brigham, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of Steve Delong, 2007...
      - Portrait of Carol Ann Germain, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of Michael Montario, 2007...
      - Portrait of David Pettie, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of John Welch, 2007...
      - Portrait of Gerald Zahavi, 2007...
      - Portrait of Hassaram Bakrhu, 2008....
      - Portrait of Michael Castellana, 2008...
      - Portrait of Mary Gallant, 2008...
      - Portrait of Carolyn MacDonald, 2008...
      - Portrait of Carol Whittaker, 2008...
      - Portrait of Mary Applegate, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Heidi Audino, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Carm Colfer, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Sharon Dawes, 2009...
      - Portrait of Dan Levy, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Dianna Newman, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Alison Olin, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Theresa Pardo, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Kelly Wissman, 2009...
      - Portrait of Thomas Bass, 2010....
      - Portrait of Judith Langer, 1996...
      - Portrait of Sharon Dawes, 1998...
      - Portrait of Christine Lemesianou, 1998...
      - Portrait of Sandra Vergari, 1998...
      - Portrait of Katharine Dovidenko, 1999...
      - Portrait of Laurie Garafola, 1999...
      - Portrait of John Justeson, 1999...
      - Portrait of Robt Osuma, 1999...
      - Portrait of Garry Sanders, 1999...
      - Portrait of Harry Wood, 1999...
      - Portrait of Thomas Birkland, 2000...
      - Portrait of Phillip Eppard, 2000...
      - Portrait of Norman Rice, c. 2000...
      - Portrait of Iliana Semmler, 2000...
      - Portrait of Carol Stenger, 2000...
      - Portrait of Rubin Arana-Downs, c. 2001...
      - Portrait of Eliot Rich, 2001...
      - Portrait of Debbie Shannon, 2001...
      - Portrait of Lisa Taylor, 2001...
      - Portrait of Chris Thorncroft, 2001...
      - Portrait of Bob Andrea, c. 2002...
      - Portrait of Tom Constantine, 2002...
      - Portrait of Paul Toscano, 2002...
      - Portrait of Laurence Kranich, c. 2003...
      - Portrait of Lee Serravillo, 2003...
      - Portrait of David Strogatz, 2003...
      - Portrait of David Andersen, 2004....
      - Portrait of Sanjay Goel, 2004...
      - Portrait of Ozgen Sayginsoy, 2004...
      - Portrait of David Strait, 2004...
      - Portrait of Kevin Wilcox, 2004...
      - Portrait of Richard Barney, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Janice Bogan, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Seth Chaiken, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Leona Christie, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Barry Davis, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Dennis Dooley, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of David Duffee, 2005...
      - Portrait of Eric Eisenbaum, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Kathy Gersowitz, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Alexandra Guerrero, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Theresa Harrison, c. 2008..., 2005
      - Portrait of Nick Henny, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Richard Highfield, c. 2008..., 2005
      - Portrait of Dick Ingles, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Istvan Kecskes, c. 2009..., 2005
      - Portrait of Nadia Kizenko, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Kelly Lamb, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Pamela Laverty, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Paul Leonard, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Adam Lifshey, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of John Logan, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Sheila Mahan, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Frank Mauro, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Steve Messner, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Charles Micchelli, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of John Monfasani, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Bob Morawski, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Leo Nevue, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Janet Perloff, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Hoang Phan, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Kathy Plunkett, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Don Putterman, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Frank Thompson, 2005...
      - Portrait of Charlie Williams, 2005...
      - Portrait of Gale Butler, c. 2006...
      - Portrait of Tyshena Hunter, c. 2006...
      - Portrait of Susan Supple, 2006...
      - Portrait of Guy Alonge, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of Kevin Bronner, 2007...
      - Portrait of Sue Faerman, 2007...
      - Portrait of James Mower, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of Saggi Navo, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of Joette Stefi-Mabry, 2007...
      - Portrait of Christine Bouchard, 2008...
      - Portrait of Nate Cady, c. 2008...
      - Portrait of Igor Kuznestov, 2008...
      - Portrait of Morris Massry, 2008...
      - Portrait of Benjamin Shaw, 2008...
      - Portrait of Sara Anderson, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Walter Gibson, 2009...
      - Portrait of Chris Ives, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Judith Langer, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Siwei Lyu, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Joan Newman, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Alex Pieterse, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Carol Rodgers, 2009...
      - Portrait of David Smith, 2009...
      - Portrait of Sandra Vergari, 2009...
      - Portrait of Senem Guney, c. 2010...
      - Portrait of Peg Aldrich, 1998....
      - Portrait of Thomas Daniels, 1998...
      - Portrait of John Jones, 1998...
      - Portrait of D'elia 1999...
      - Portrait of John Fallon, c. 1999...
      - Portrait of Gary Gossen, 1999...
      - Portrait of Anne McGill-Franzen, 1999...
      - Portrait of Kim Sprague, 1999...
      - Portrait of Edward Blanchard, 2000...
      - Portrait of Catherine T. Lawson, 2000...
      - Portrait of Susan Sherman, 2000...
      - Portrait of Cathy Widom, 2000...
      - Portrait of Pina Smith, 2001...
      - Portrait of Jim Thomas, 2001...
      - Portrait of Hans Tocha, 2001...
      - Portrait of Jim Wyckoff, 2001...
      - Portrait of Helen Desfosses, 2002...
      - Portrait of Ivan Steen, 2002...
      - Portrait of Harriet Temps, 2002...
      - Portrait of Linda Wheeler, 2002...
      - Portrait of Gerald Marschke, c. 2003...
      - Portrait of Barry Trachtenberg, 2003...
      - Portrait of Victor Asal, c. 2004...
      - Portrait of Thomas A. Constantine, 2005..., 2004
      - Portrait of Tom Galvin, 2004...
      - Portrait of John Ryan, 2004...
      - Portrait of Miriam Trementozzi, 2004...
      - Portrait of Penelope Benson-Wright, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Mike Boots, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Christine Bouchard, c. 2008..., 2005
      - Portrait of Lindsey Childs, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Elizabeth Close, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Jeff Collins, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Christy DeLaMater, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Nancy Denton, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Mehgan Dougherty, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Judy Euler, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Mark Fisher, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Michele Flynn, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Joachim Frank, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Jagdish Gangolly, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Harold Gould, 2005...
      - Portrait of Richard Hall, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Karen Hitchcock, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of David Janower, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Alain Kaloyeros, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Rey Koslowski, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of T.S. Kuan, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Peter Levin, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of P.D. Magnus, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Maritza Martinez, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Yvette Mattern, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Lee McElroy, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Antun Milas, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Michelle Moshier, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Richard Nathan, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Deb Oriola, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Susan Phillips, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of George Richardson, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of James Anderson, 2006....
      - Portrait of Karen Murdock, c. 2006...
      - Portrait of David Bobrek, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of Kevin Knuth, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of Gerald Shaye, 2007...
      - Portrait of Margaret Stewart, 2007...
      - Portrait of Aaron Benavot, c. 2008...
      - Portrait of Michael Bloom, 2008...
      - Portrait of Babu Guda, 2008...
      - Portrait of Lawrence Lessner, 2008...
      - Portrait of Claudia Ricci, c. 2008...
      - Portrait of Leonard Slade, 2008...
      - Portrait of Yuchi Young, 2008...
      - Portrait of Joe Bowman, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Maureen Cohan, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Michael Ellis, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Gina Giuliano, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Daniel Hogarty, 2009...
      - Portrait of Bill McCann, 2009...
      - Portrait of Andres Posada, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Sharon Wiles, 2009...
      - Portrait of Vince O'Leary, 2010...
      - Portrait of JoEllen Welsh, 2010...
      - Portrait of Marilyn Masson, 1996...
      - Portrait of James Fleming, 1997...
      - Portrait of Susan Blood, 1998...
      - Portrait of Vesna Gjaja, 1998...
      - Portrait of Gerard Marshke, 1998...
      - Portrait of Renee Sieber, 1998...
      - Portrait of Saurav Dutta, 1999...
      - Portrait of Gary Jacobson, 1999...
      - Portrait of Andrei Lapenis, 1999...
      - Portrait of Roger Stump, 1999...
      - Portrait of Wendy Wang, 1999...
      - Portrait of Walter Zenner, 1999...
      - Portrait of Jane Domaracki, 2000...
      - Portrait of Istvan Kaesckes, 2000...
      - Portrait of Tang Rong, 2000...
      - Portrait of Paul Stec, 2000...
      - Portrait of Lance Bosart, 2001...
      - Portrait of JoAnn Menzer, c. 2001...
      - Portrait of Latonia Spencer, 2001...
      - Portrait of Mary Unser, 2001...
      - Portrait of Arthur Applebee, 2002....
      - Portrait of Jagdish Gangolly, 2002...
      - Portrait of Debra Rock, 2002...
      - Portrait of Ronald Canestrari, 2003...
      - Portrait of John Jones, c. 2003...
      - Portrait of Dale Morse, 2003...
      - Portrait of Carol Richardson-Rogers, 2000..., 2003
      - Portrait of Len Slade, 2003...
      - Portrait of Wayne Ramie, 2003...
      - Portrait of David Andersen, 2004...
      - Portrait of Scott South, 2004...
      - Portrait of Kate Winter, 2004...
      - Portrait of Roberta Bernstein, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Anne Boehm, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Meredith Butler, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Carson Carr, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Delores Cimini, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Bill Ding, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Joseph Edmondson, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Cynthia Fox, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Susan Gauss, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Sanjay Goel, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Theresa Greaves, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Hal Gueutal, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Alethia Jones, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of William Kennedy, ca 2009..., 2005
      - Portrait of Christian-Paul Lenart, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of David Lewis, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Kathy Lowery, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Anne Marfey, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Janet Marler, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Ellie Moore, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Joyce Carol Oates, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Jennifer Orton, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Vinny Reda, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Christine Smith, 2005...
      - Portrait of Mary Valentis, 2005...
      - Portrait of Laura Fredriksen, c. 2006...
      - Portrait of Linda Krzycowski, c. 2006...
      - Portrait of Bernie Arbit, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of Peter Bloniarz, 2007...
      - Portrait of Jennifer Carron, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of Lorre Smith, 2007...
      - Portrait of Janet Stamatel, 2007...
      - Portrait of Deirdre Sweeney, 2007...
      - Portrait of David Wojeski, 2007...
      - Portrait of Joseph Zimmerman, 2001..., 2007
      - Portrait of Christine Bouchard, 2008...
      - Portrait of Courtney D'Allaird, c. 2008...
      - Portrait of Michael Range, c. 2008...
      - Portrait of Brenda Seckerson, 2008...
      - Portrait of Donald Siegel, 2008...
      - Portrait of Edelgard Wulfert, 2008...
      - Portrait of Jane Domarackie, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of JeanPierre Abner, 2009...
      - Portrait of Jason Lane, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Sheila Meissner, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Mary Murphy, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Ruth Pagerey, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Bob Pruzek, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Joshua Sussman, 2009...
      - Portrait of Alan Wagner, 2009...
      - Portrait of Aja Case, c. 2010...
      - Portrait of Deborah Andersen 1998....
      - Portrait of Francois Cooren, 1998...
      - Portrait of Amy Lehman, 1998...
      - Portrait of Shadd Maruna, 1998...
      - Portrait of Edwin Aquilar, 1999....
      - Portrait of Chris D'Elia, 1999...
      - Portrait of Kristy Gugel, 1999...
      - Portrait of Sandra Matheson,..., 1999
      - Portrait of Sheila Mahan, 1999
      - Portrait of Jim Morris, c. 1999...
      - Portrait of Bonnie Steinbock, 1999...
      - Portrait of Bai Xu, 1999...
      - Portrait of Kristy Gugle, 2000...
      - Portrait of Marcia Moody, 2000...
      - Portrait of Jennifer Rudolph, 2000...
      - Portrait of Carlos Santiago, 2001...
      - Portrait of Pat Swygert, 2001...
      - Portrait of Terrance Thornberry, 2001...
      - Portrait of Silke VanNess, 2001...
      - Portrait of Gene Schuler, 2002...
      - Portrait of Tomek Stzralkowski, 2002...
      - Portrait of Lynn Videka, 2002...
      - Portrait of Carol Anderson, c. 2003...
      - Portrait of Michael Jerison, c. 2003...
      - Portrait of Yun Kwan Koo, c. 2003...
      - Portrait of Rui Zhao, 2003...
      - Portrait of Ron Berger, c. 2004...
      - Portrait of Dana Peterson, c. 2004...
      - Portrait of Judith Saidel, 2004...
      - Portrait of Paul Schurr, 2004...
      - Portrait of Hedy Bagatelle, c. 2005...
      - Portrait of Wendy Becker, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Jeff Berman, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Debbie Brown, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Laura Cohen, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Jakov Crnkovic, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Vincent Delio, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Mary Jo Dougherty, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Catherine Dwyer, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Christophe Faugere, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of John Forsyth, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Tim Gage, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Annis Golden, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Kermit Hall, c. 2005...
      - Portrait of Ed Hannan, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Jill Harbeck, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of William Holstein, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Hayward Horton, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Dennis Kennedy, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Gail Landsman, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Catherine Lawson, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Max Lifchitz, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Walter Little, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Sophie Lubensky, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Tony Manes, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Adrian Masters, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Sarah McCarthy, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Candace Merbler, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Jeryl Mumpower, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Elena Nelson, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Anita Pomeantz, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Marjorie Pryse, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Bill Rainbolt, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of David Rousseau, 2005...
      - Portrait of Ron Toseland, 2005...
      - Portrait of Sho-Ya Wang, 2005...
      - Portrait of Neil Pischner, c. 2006...
      - Portrait of Robert Apel, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of Kevin Knuth, 2007...
      - Portrait of Jeremy Atkinson, c. 2008...
      - Portrait of Joel Berkowitz, c. 2008...
      - Portrait of Timothy Hoff, 2008...
      - Portrait of Jennifer Manganello, 2008...
      - Portrait of Phillip Nasca, 2008...
      - Portrait of Shadi Saleh, 2008...
      - Portrait of Wendy Weller, 2008...
      - Portrait of Dwight Williams, 2008...
      - Portrait of Janet Angelis, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Theresa Femia, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Jennifer Hogan, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Eric Lifshin, 2009...
      - Portrait of Linda Papa, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Rebecca Salinas, 2009...
      - Portrait of Zheng Yan, 2009...
      - Portrait of James Fleming, 1997...
      - Portrait of Tim Hoff, 1998...
      - Portrait of Neal Mark, 1998...
      - Portrait of Liz Wright, 1998...
      - Portrait of Cheryl Frye, 1998..., 1999
      - Portrait of Boris Goldfarb, 1999...
      - Portrait of June Hahner, 1999...
      - Portrait of Mary Jane Highfield, 1999...
      - Portrait of Anne McGill-Franzen, 1999...
      - Portrait of Debbi Nuls, 1999...
      - Portrait of Kathrine Schiller, 1999...
      - Portrait of Frank Vellutino, 1999...
      - Portrait of Vince Aceto, 2000....
      - Portrait of Debbie Archambeault, c. 2000...
      - Portrait of Mina Devadas, 2000...
      - Portrait of Don Putterman, 2000...
      - Portrait of Kinsun Tam, 2000...
      - Portrait of Margarita Rodriguez, 2001...
      - Portrait of Giri Tayi, 2001...
      - Portrait of Daniel Trujillo, 2001...
      - Portrait of Susan Hughes, 2003...
      - Portrait of John J. McEneny, 2003...
      - Portrait of Cheryl Savini, 2003...
      - Portrait of Marc Carter, c. 2004...
      - Portrait of Pradeep Haldar, c. 2004...
      - Portrait of Phillip Nasca, 2004...
      - Portrait of Shobha Smith, 2004...
      - Portrait of Suzanne Traylor, 2004...
      - Portrait of Rita Biswas, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Ray Bromley, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Tom Brutsaert, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Audry Champagne, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Felicia Collins, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Nicholas Conway, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Trishul Devineni, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Saurav Dutta, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Mary Fritz, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Laurie Garafola, 2005...
      - Portrait of Zvi Gellis, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Alice Green, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Gunnarsson family, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Craig Hancock, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Tasharni Harris, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Susan Herbst, c. 2007..., 2005
      - Portrait of Monica Hope, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of John Jacklet, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Eric Keenaghan, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of D. Ekow King, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Eleanor Leggieri, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of William Luca, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Jackie Marino, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Marilyn Masson, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Nick Mastracchio, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Ann McGill-Franzen, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Carla Meskill, c. 2009..., 2005
      - Portrait of John Molinari, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Paliath Narendran, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Andrew Neiderman, 2005...
      - Portrait of Michael Parker, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Stephen Phelps, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Tyrone Reid, c. 2005....
      - Portrait of Larry Schell, 2005...
      - Portrait of Mike Smith, 2005...
      - Portrait of Richard Wilkerson, 2005...
      - Portrait of Michael Christakis, c. 2006...
      - Portrait of Blanche Feck, c. 2006...
      - Portrait of Kathleen Thornton, 2006...
      - Portrait of Geoffrey Williams, 2006...
      - Portrait of Robert Bangert-Drowns, 2007....
      - Portrait of Tim Bruculere, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of John Fallon, 2007...
      - Portrait of Melissa Hubbard, c. 2007...
      - Portrait of James Mower, 2007...
      - Portrait of Abebe Rorissa, 2007...
      - Portrait of Wei-Chyung Wang, 2007...
      - Portait of Frances Allen, c. 2008...
      - Portrait of Erin Bell, 2008....
      - Portrait of Rabi Musah, c. 2008...
      - Portrait of Karl Schlegel, 2008...
      - Portrait of Margi Sheehy, 2009..., 2008
      - Portrait of Michael Stein, 2008...
      - Portrait of Robert Bangert-Drowns, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Gina Cosgrove, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Cheryl Dozier, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Lisa Grippo-Gardiner, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Maciej Kucharczyk, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Sanford Levine, 2009...
      - Portrait of Barbara Miller, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Elizabeth Norton, c. 2009...
      - Portrait of Warren Roberts, 2009...
      - Portrait of Bruce Saddler, 2009...
      - Portrait of Jogindar Uppal, 2009...
      - Portrait of Stacy Williams, 2009...
    - Faculty Staff, 2006 June 1-2016 July 6; 7.2; 758 Digital Files
      - Ctr. For Compartive Genomics: 10/10/01 @ 9:30 AM East Campus/ B231 staff photos for website digital, 2001 October 24; 32.0 MB 53 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 11/25/02 @ 3 PM UAB 300 portrait: Betty Morinelli digital, 2002 December 4; 6.3 MB 5 Digital Files
      - Albany NanoTech: 4/16/03 @ 9 AM CESTM new employees digital, 2003 April 17; 11.7 MB 30 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 8/26/03 @ 10 AM Management Services Rm 100 Marybeth Salmon digital, 2003 September 8; 136.5 MB 46 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 8/26/03 @ 10 AM Management Services Rm 100 Marybeth Salmon digital, 2003 September 8; 136.5 MB 46 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 10/22/03 @ 9 AM PAC Finley Cockrell riding scooter digital, 2003 November 5; 43.0 MB 6 Digital Files
      - Portraits, 2003 November 5; 128.1 MB 93 Digital Files
      - Media and Marketing: 10/22/03 @ 9 AM PAC Finley Cockrell riding scooter digital, 2003 November 5; 43.0 MB 6 Digital Files
      - Portraits, 2003 November 5; 49.3 MB 37 Digital Files